<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="6dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="21dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#aa0909" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="Benefits of Surya Bhedana Pranayama:"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="                     \n1. This type of yogic breathing influences brains activity in different ways.                     \n\n2. Surya Bhedana Pranayama activates the body and bodily functions.                     \n\n3. The digestive fire is increased by this pranayama.                     \n\n4. It destroys all diseases that are caused by the insufficiency of oxygen in the blood.                     \n\n5. Surya Bhide Pranayama has also effects on shooting ability in Basketball players. (study)                     \n\n6. The Hath Yoga says that Surya Bhedana Pranayama cleans the frontal sinuses, destroys disorders of Vata, and destroys intestinal worms.                     \n\n7. Activates and stimulates the pranic energy by energizing the Pingala Nadi.                     \n\n8. It helps alleviate dullness, lethargy, and depression.                     \n\n9. Brings fresh energy to the body so one can perform physical activities more efficiently.                     \n\n10. Useful in treating low blood pressure and infertility in women.                     \n\n11. It increases body temperature, thus removing the Kafa (mucus) imbalance. This is very effective in obesity. Regular practice of right nostril breath is helpful in weight loss.                     \n\n12. Very effective for stress management.                     \n\n13. It helps reducing anxiety, depression, and other mental illnesses.                     \n\n14. Balancing Ida and Pingala removes all the blockages in the pranic energy channels, which may lead to spiritual awakenings.                     \n\n15. It gives all the benefits of deep breathing as well."/>
            <TextView android:textSize="21dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#aa0909" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="\nPrecaution for Surya Bhedana:"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text=" \n\n1. Surya Bhedana pranayama should be practiced on an empty stomach.  \n\n2. All the inhalations should be done through the right nostril and exhalations through the left.  \n\n3. It should be done in the morning or evening or both. If you don’t have the time in the morning or evening, you can do it at your own convenience.  \n\n4. Make sure that you practice Surya Bhedana pranayama 4–5 hours after having your food.  \n\n5. Inhalation and exhalation should be in the ratio of 1:2.  \n\n6. If you feel even a little bit of discomfort then you can reduce the ratio of breathing.  \n\n7. People suffering from heart disease, high blood pressure or epilepsy should avoid this Pranayam.  \n\n8. People who have undergone brain surgeries, heart surgeries or abdominal surgeries should consult the medical expert or consultant before doing this Pranayam.  \n\n9. This pranayama increases the heat of your body so it should be avoided if suffering from fever.\n"/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
