<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="6dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="21dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#aa0909" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="Benefits of Sheetali Pranayama:"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="                     \n1. The act of pulling the air via the tongue creates a cooling effect on the body. \n\n2. This pranayama relaxes both the mind and the body. \n\n3. As per hath Yoga, it can cure fever as well as disorders of the bile. \n\n4. It helps in the control and removal of hunger and thirst. \n\n5. This Practise is quite useful in pitta related diseases. \n\n6. It is also effective in hyperactivity. \n\n7. This practice of Pranayama helps in keeping the digestive system fine. If our digestion is good, then all stomach related diseases can be got rid of. \n\n8. If you are suffering from depression, then you should practice this pranayama. It acts as a panacea in reducing depression. \n\n9. It is quite beneficial in diseases of the spleen. \n\n10. This pranayama conquers hunger, thirst, fever (fever) and tuberculosis. \n\n11. It can be used as a pacifier before sleeping. \n\n12. According to yoga science, the regular practice of this pranayama for a long time has no effect of poison or snake bite on the person. \n\n13. If your BP or blood pressure is increased then you can reduce high blood pressure by practicing Sheetali Pranayama. \n\n14. It helps in fighting against the problem of insomnia. \n\n15. Irritability, anger in the talk, tension and warm nature are especially beneficial for individuals. \n\n16. Regulates the secretion of hormones in the genitals. And reduces the mental and emotional effects of lust. \n\n17. By practicing this pranayama regularly, you can get rid of your eye problem soon. \n\n18. By practicing this pranayama, we can reduce the mental and emotional excitement and spasticity of mind. \n\n19. Complaints of excessive sweating also provide relief. \n\n20. This pranayama is like a shady tree which produces plenty of oxygen."/>
            <TextView android:textSize="21dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#aa0909" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="\nPrecaution for Sheetali:"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text=" \n1. In case you have low blood pressure then this pranayama can essentially bring down it even further. So you have to be quite careful about it. \n\n2. You may also feel a little bit of cold or tingling sensation in your throat due to the cold air, but this is normal. \n\n3. In case you feel dizzy then you should stop the practice of this pranayama and start the normal breathing. \n\n4. the case of those who suffer from Asthma, cold, cough or other respiratory-related problem, they shouldn’t try this pranayama. \n\n5. One should avoid doing this pranayama during the extremely cold days.\n"/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
