<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="4dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="                     \n1. Bhramari pranayama helps in, effective as well as instant calming down of the mind. It is considered to be among the best breathing exercises to release the mind from all the agitation along with frustration or anxiety as well as getting rid of anger.                     \n\n2. Bhramari word has its origin from the Sanskrit word Bhramar which means humming bee. In this particular pranayama, the humming sound is created which is why the name Bhramari. The most evident effect of this pranayama is that it relaxes the brain. If this pranayama is done on a regular basis, one can have a positive effect on his mind by getting rid of stress, fatigue as well as high blood pressure. This practice also helps in ear, nose, mouth as well as eyes related problems.                     \n\n3. A scientific study suggests Bharmari pranayama along with Udgeeth Pranayama improves pulmonary function.                     \n\n4. Bhramari pranayama is quite useful in curing migraines as well as paralysis. People of all ages can easily perform this breathing exercise, even the pregnant women. During the pregnancy period, if a woman performs this, it can help her in maintaining as well as regulating the functioning of the endocrine system. It also helps her in trouble-free and easy childbirth.                     \n\n5. Bhramari pranayama is generally performed after completion of  Anulom Vloma Pranayama  in order to obtain its fullest potential."/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
