<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="4dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text=" \n1. Pranayama also has its own special importance in yoga. It is very beneficial for staying healthy both mentally and physically. Practicing Pranayama can help in getting rid of many serious diseases. One of these processes involved in pranayama is Bhastrika Pranayama.  \n\n2. Bhastrika Pranayama Yoga is a combination of two Sanskrit words. The first word is Bhastrika, which means ‘bellows’. The blower is the device that a blacksmith uses to accelerate the heat of the coal. At the same time, Pranayama means that the life of the air is expanding.  \n\n3. Bhastrika is such pranayama in which pure air is taken inside and impure air is thrown out at a fast speed. Which looks similar to Kapalbhati but it is very different both.  \n\n4. Bhastrika pranayama is a breathing technique known to produce heat in the body. Bhastrika is powerful and energetic pranayama in yoga breathing practice. Kapalbhati is also a breathing technique that mimics sneezing and involves the stomach, but Bhastrika is through the chest and engages the lungs. This is one of the best techniques which will remove the blockage from all Nadis.  \n\n5. Bhastrika pranayama is a panacea treatment to overcome the problems of Vata, Pitta, and Kapha. Its long-term healing purifies the blockages from the chakras. Performing this Pranayama asana is beneficial for heart and brain patients to achieve a miraculous magnitude.  \n\n6. Now it comes to how to do Bhastrika Pranayama. Here it is explained in a simple way, with the help of which you can do it easily."/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
