<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="4dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="21dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#aa0909" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="\nHow to Start Ujjayi Pranayam: "/>
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text=" \n1. Ujjayi pranayama stretches as well as warms the breath before it enters into the lungs. This assists in generating heat which is effective in getting rid of toxins present in the body.  \n\n2. Both inhalation and exhalation are performed through the nostrils. The breath is directed to the throat’s back while it constricts the muscles which cause a hissing sound similar to the sound of an ocean which is why it is also known as Ocean Breath. As the throat’s passage is made narrower, the airspeed is increased.  \n\n3. This pranayama requires mild glottis contraction along with upper opening part of your larynx and closing partially it through the epiglottis just like it generally happens while swallowing. By doing this during inhalation and exhalation of the air through both of the nostrils, a “sound of hissing ”- like an aspirant “hhh” sound is produced.  \n\n4. However, this sound shouldn’t be too strong as it might bring strain to the vocal cords, but it should just be audible to the practitioner. Both inhalation and exhalation should be, long as well as deep, and in the ratio of 1:2.  \n\n5. Ujjayi pranayama can easily be done for any length of time. It can be as few as 12 cycles on a regular basis which provides immense benefits to you but if it is practiced for 10-12 minutes daily the effect is trans formative. No matter what time length you maintain, it is essential that the breath should remain slow, fluid, gentle as well as relaxed throughout the practice.  \n\n6. When you are ready to complete the practice, do it by complete exhalation and then release the constriction at the throat’s back and then finally complete one or two more full Yogic Breaths. Then, bring your breath back to the normal. Take a moment in order to notice the effects of the practice."/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
