<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="4dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="21dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#aa0909" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="\nHow to Start Surya Bhedana Pranayam: "/>
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="     \n1. Steps 1: Asana     \nSurya Bhedana Pranayama should be practiced in a quiet environment. This Pranayama proves to be more fruitful in clean natural air. Therefore, by first choosing the best place, place a mat there and place it in the normal posture.      \n\nSteps 2: Yogic Sitting Posture     \nFirst of all, sit in a cross-legged position on the yoga mat. You have to sit in the posture of Padmasana, that is, keep the paws of the left foot on your right thigh and the paws of the right foot on the left thigh. Those who cannot sit in Padmasana posture, they can sit in Sukhasana posture. At the same time, those who are difficult to sit on the ground, they can sit on the chair.      \n\nSit in a comfortable pose. We advise you to sit with your backbone straight and make sure you fill breath in the lungs. Keep both your hands on your knees. Now forget all the worries of your mind. Keep the waist straight and close both your eyes. And try to concentrate on yourself.      \n\nSteps 3: Yogic Hand Gesture     \nRight hand gesture:-  Make Vishnu Mudra with the right hand.      \n\nVishnu Mudra is practice with the right hand. In this mudra, both the index finger and the middle finger have to be touched with the root of the thumb. Apart from this, the rest of the fingers are upright. This mudra stimulated the first three chakras – The Muladhara, Svadisthana, and Manipura.      \n\nThis hand gesture called Vishnu Mudra (symbol of Vishnu), which is used to breathe through the nose during the Nadi Shodhana. Because some pranayama techniques say one nostril to breathe at a time, while the other nostril is lightly closed. This mudra always uses for Nadi Shodan Pranayama.      \n\nLeft-hand gesture:- Make Gyan mudra with the left hand and put it on the left fingers and place it over the kneecap.      \n\nSteps 4: Breathing Process     \nIn Surya Bhedana (Right Nostril Breathing) pranayama, inhalation is done only through Right nostril and exhalation is done only through Left Nostril. The thumb is used to close the right nostril and the ring finger is used to close the left nostril.      \n\nChoose a level of exercise, you can easily keep up with and breathe comfortably.      \n\nSet your value for inhaling, exhale and hold.     \nA ratio of Inhale, Hold and Exhale is 1:4:2. The ratio 1:4:2 is mentioned in most classic.      \n\ninhale = x sec      \n\nexhale = 2inhale = 2x sec      \n\nhold = 2exhale = 4x sec      \n\nhold = 2exhale = 4x sec      \n\nPranayama beginners should start with the ratio of 1:1 for inhaling and exhale. For instance, if you inhale through one nostril for 4 seconds, then the exhalation from the other nostril should also be for 4 seconds. As you progress, the ratio for inhaling and exhaling can be changed to 1:2, which means if inhalation is 4 seconds, then exhalation is 8 seconds.      \n\nSome simple steps to do-      \n\n1. Close the left nostril, using your finger and start breathing in. Try to use full seconds.      \n\n2. Hold both nostrils, using your thumb and ring finger, and hold your breath.      \n\n3. Open your left nostril and breath out slowly and steadily.      \n\n4. Repeat from Step 1.      \n\nSteps 5: Time Sessions     \nWhen you start doing Surya bhadhana, the process of breathing, hold and exhaling should be done 5 to 10 times at the initial stage."/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
