<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="6dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="21dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#aa0909" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="Benefits of Kapalbhati Pranayama:"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="                     \n1. The breathing technique involves &apos;active exhalation and passive inhalation&apos;. During inhalation the stomach sinks in and vice-versa during exhaling. This stomach movement is therefore beneficial for the muscles around it, including that of the liver and pancreas. The blood flow to these areas also increases.                      \n\n2. It aids digestion and removal of acidity and gas related problems.                      \n\n3. Regular practice of kapalbhati is also beneficial for belly fat loss.                      \n\n4. The technique involves forceful breathing which strengthens lungs and increases its capacity.                      \n\n5. &apos;Practicing Kapalbhati helps in removing blockages in the heart and lungs&apos;.                      \n\n6. It also increases blood supply to various parts of the body.                      \n\n7. It activates the body and removes lethargy. Facial radiance is a natural benefit as the name suggests.                      \n\n8. It activates the brain cells and improves memory and concentration power.                      \n\n9. Kapalbhati is great for focus and checks forgetfulness.                      \n\n10. Kapalbhati has spiritual paybacks as well. It activates the chakras in the body and helps in achieving a higher, greater awakening."/>
            <TextView android:textSize="21dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#aa0909" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="\nPrecaution for Kapalbhati:"/>
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="                     \n1. You must also take some precautions while performing It. If you do this pranayama in the wrong ways, then neurological problems and heart-related diseases can occur. Kapalbhati Pranayama should not be done in some cases.                      \n\n2. Kapalbhati Pranayam should be done on an empty stomach in the morning. If you have eaten food then do it after 4-5 hours. After doing this, do not eat anything for at least 20 minutes.                      \n\n3. Those who are doing yoga for the first time, start It under the supervision of an expert. It must be ensured that the steps of doing the are correct.                      \n\n4. Kapalbhati exercises can be done by people of all age groups, but those who have respiratory problems should do this asana only after the advice of a doctor.                      \n\n5. If a woman is pregnant, then she should avoid doing Kapalbhati Pranayama.                      \n\n6. If you are a patient of heart disease, then while breathing Kapalbhati Pranayama, do not breathe lightly or else you do not do this pranayama.                      \n\n7. Apart from this, people who have any disease like heart disease, high blood pressure or hernia, then they should not practice Kapalbhati.                      \n\n8. Do any yoga activity according to your ability, do not insist on seeing others, do not do much in enthusiasm.\n"/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
