<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="4dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="                     \n1. Kapalbhati yoga has a method of hatha yoga. It is the best of the 6 Yoga Kriyas (Shatkarma) mentioned in the Yoga Granth Ghernda Samhita.                      \n\n2. 6 Yogic Kriyas (Shatkarma) are:-  Netī, Dhautī, Naulī, Basti, Kapālabhātī, and Trāṭaka.                      \n\n3. Nati for nasal wash, Dhauti for cleansing digestive tract, Nauli for abdominal massage, Basti for colonic irrigation, Kapalbhati for balancing the nadis and the chakras, and Trataka for strengthening eyes.                      \n\n4. The word Kapalbhati is from the Sanskrit language. Where Kapal “means forehead (the front part of the brain is called the skull) and the meaning of the ” Bhati ” is ‘shining, illuminating’Now it comes to Pranayama, then Pranayama is one of the eight organs of yoga. Ashtanga yoga consists of eight processes. (eight limbs of yoga)                      \n\n5. Pranayama = Prana + Ayam. It literally means ‘prolonging of prana (respiration)’ or ‘prolonging prana (sustenance)’. (Pranayama does not mean ‘to control the breath’ or to reduce it.) Pranayam is the dimension or expansion of the breath. It gives life force to a person by the flow of prana-shakti.                      \n\n6. The important Shatkarma Kapalbhati Pranayama also called the breath of fire. And Another name is ‘Bhalabhati’ where Bhala stands for Head and the meaning of the ” Bhati ” is light.  This advanced breathing technique sometimes referred to as “Light Skull Breathing”. ( Hatha yoga pradipika)                      \n\n7. This yogic breathing technique or “Cleaning Breath” involves short and strong forceful exhalations and inhalation.                      \n\n8. On another note, Kapalbhati is one of the rapid breathing techniques as well as automatic inhalation techniques and forced inhalation."/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
