<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="4dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" 
                android:text="\n1. It is also Known as Nadi Shodhan (Alternate Nostril Breathing). The left nostril is Ida (moon principle or mind), Right nostril represents Pingala Nadi (Sun principle or body).                     
                              \n\n2. In alternate nostril breathing, once inhale through Left and exhale through Right then inhale through Right and exhale through Left Nostril. This purifies the Ida and Pingala Nadis.
                              \n\n3. The purpose of the Alternate Nostril Breathing is to balance the physical and mental energy. It is recommended for all types of problems. As Hatha Yoga principle says that the health conditions are due to an imbalance between these Ida and Pingala Nadis, alternate nostril breathing balances these two forces.
                              \n\n4. It is very effective in purifying the mind and body. Regular practice offers energy to the body, releases stress, anxiety and also treat serious health conditions, which include heart problems, cartilage, depression, asthma, high blood pressure, and arthritis. Some of the practitioners also recommend AnulomVilom Pranayam for the treatment of bent ligaments, neural issues, migraine pain, and sinus. It should be practiced in the morning in the fresh air with an empty stomach.                     \n\n5. It can also reduce weight depending on the body constitution as this Pranayam is very good for obesity. Anulom Viloma Pranayama ensures proper supply of energy to all the body organs enhancing the overall health of the body.                     \n\n6.There are many reasons to do Nadishodana Anuloma Viloma (Alternate Nostril Breathing) pranayama. By practicing a few rounds of Nadishodhana  Anuloma Viloma pranayama each day for few minutes can help us control our conscious to some extent.                     \n\n7. Anulom Viloma pranayama can be performed without holding of breath. For beginners, it is advisable to practice the Anulom Viloma Pranayama without holding of breath."/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
