<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="4dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="                     \n1. Sheetali Pranayama, as its name suggests, is related to coldness. It provides coolness to our body. Hence it is also called Cooling Breath.  \n\n2. The word “Sheetali” is actually a Sanskrit word which means cooling. It is being taken from the original word “Sheetal” which means cold or soothing. There are great benefits of this pranayama. Sheetali Pranayama is an integral part of Pranayama. Which enables both performing controlled breathing yoga and calming the mind for meditation. This pranayama should be done after all the yogasanas, by doing this, the body’s tiredness is removed and remains in the body. Apart from this, it also provides peace of mind. This pranayama is like a shady tree which produces plenty of oxygen.  \n\n3. The most basic purpose of Sheetali breathing technique is that it reduces the temperature of the body which does have a positive effect on the endocrine glands as well as the nervous system.  \n\n4. According to the ancient text of Hath Yoga, the person who practices this pranayama becomes both young as well as attractive. It is also said that this pranayama is great in removing excess heat which is accumulated in the system. It also reduces excess biles. And also corrects the disorders of the spleen and works on fever too. Sheetali pranayama also provides control over hunger as well as thirst.  \n\n5. It has quite a soothing effect on the entire nervous system of the human body, especially in stimulation of the parasympathetic nervous system which also induces muscular relaxation and hence it is quite effective in the stress management. In case you are stressed then by simply practicing 10 minutes of Sheetali breathing can essentially calm your mind. This pranayama is quite effective in relaxation of both the mind and the body.  \n\n6. It has been prominently described in ancient and rare Yoga texts like Yoga Kundalyopanishad, Hatha Yoga Pradipika, and Gherand Samhita. Many people have benefited from this and are becoming.  \n\n7. Sheetali pranayama or the cooling breath is often done after practicing other asanas as well as pranayamas."/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
