<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="4dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="21dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#aa0909" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="\nHow to Start Kapalbhati Pranayam: "/>
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="                     \n1. To begin, sit in a comfortable position where your spine is straight and your abdomen is not compressed. Some options include:                     \n\9\9\91. An upright seated position, such as Easy Pose (Sukhasana)                     \n\9\9\92. Sitting on your heels, with your knees bent and shins tucked beneath your thighs in Hero Pose (Virasana)                     \n\9\9\93. A seated position on a chair with your feet flat on the floor                     \n\n2. Rest your hands on your knees, palms facing down.                     \n\n3. Bring your awareness to your lower belly. To heighten your awareness, you can place your hands, one on top of the other, on your lower belly rather than on your knees.                     \n\n4. Inhale through both nostrils deeply.                     \n\n5. Contract your low belly or use your hands to gently press on this area, forcing out the breath in a short burst.                     \n\n6. As you quickly release the contraction, your inhalation should be automatic and passive — your focus should be on exhaling.                     \n\n7. Begin slowly, aiming for 65-70 contractions per minute. Gradually quicken the pace, aiming for 95-105 exhalation/inhalation cycles per minute. Always go at your own pace and stop if you feel faint or dizzy.                     \n\n8. After one minute of the exercise, inhale deeply through the nostrils, and then exhale slowly through your mouth. Depending on your experience level, you may repeat the exercise."/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
