<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android" android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:layout_marginLeft="4dp">
            <TextView android:textSize="14dp" android:textStyle="bold" android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent" android:text="                     \nIt is also known as 4:7:8 Breathing.  \n\nThis is one of the most primitive and common techniques practiced by people all around the world. This technique helps to relax, calm down your tensed muscles and wash out the stress in your mind and body to help you sleep well.  \n\nThe word meditation doesn’t appeal to many. But in its true essence, meditation is another name for corrective breathing which relaxes the mind-body-soul and induces a restful sleep.  \n\nDo not do more than four breaths of this exercise at a time for the first month of practice. Although you can do the exercise in any position, while learning this exercise it’s recommended to sit with your back straight. Holding the breath will allow oxygen to fill in your lungs and then circulate throughout the body, thus the most important part of this process is holding of breath for 8 seconds. due to this that produces a relaxing effect on the body. It can also be used to help in dealing with the cravings and to control anger. It can also improve digestion and stop the ‘fight or flight’ response in the body, lowering stress levels.  \n\nThe absolute time you spend on each phase is not important;  the ratio of 4:7:8 is important. By drawing out you inhale over 4 counts, you are making yourself slowly and consciously take in more oxygen. Then by holding your breath for 7 counts, you allow as much of that oxygen to saturate into your bloodstream as possible, energizing and cleansing all your tissues, organs and cells. Finally, by exhaling for 8 counts, you make sure that you have expelled as much carbon dioxide as possible from your lungs.  \n\nThe 4:7:8 breathing technique basically turns the shallow oxygen-poor breathing you normally do when you are stressed out upside down. This has some profound effects on your body and your mind."/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
